

- +639155939354
- rmpanis2@gmail.com
- https://romeo-portfolio.vercel.app
- Naga City, Camarines Sur, Philippines, 4400
- in linkedin.com/in/romeo-panis-ii

# **EDUCATION**

Ateneo de Naga University
 BS Information Technology
 2020 - 2024

### **EXPERTISE**

Web Development

NodeJS ReactJS SQL/NONSQL Javascript CSS

Programming Languages

C++ Java

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### O NodeJS Basic

HackerRank, March 29, 2024 Relevant skills: Javascript, NodeJS, OOP, Rest API

#### CSS Basic

HackerRank, March 29, 2024 Relevant skills: Javascript, Cascading Style Sheet

#### Introduction to Python

Datacamp, December 2023 Relevant skills: Python, R, Data Analysis, SQL, Database

# Cloud Foundations

GreatLearning Academy,
December 2023
Relevant skills: Cloud Computing,
Amazon Web Services (AWS)

# **ROMEO M. PANIS II**

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A software engineer experienced in developing web applications through NodeJS, ReactJS, and Ruby on Rails. Developed MERN Stack Web Application during my internship, wrote technical documentation, and implemented coding practices and web application architectural patterns.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

O Jan 2024 to April 2024 Network Operations and Computer Services Ateneo De Naga University

# Junior full-stack Developer and Junior System Administrator | INTERNSHIP

- Developed a web system using MERN Stack that helped the organization save thousands of dollars, and provided a seamless attendance monitoring system.
- Deployed web application on a Server with RHEL OS (ALMA LINUX) Implemented server security features (ClamAV, Iptables, etc.)
- Implemented web security features (CORS, Input validations, etc.)
- Wrote technical documentation and coding practices to aid the future development and improvement of the application.

#### Relevant Skills:

Docker, Linux commands, NodeJS, ReactJS, Javascript, MongoDB, REST API, Web security features, Architectural patterns.

#### **CAPSTONE PROJECT**

**Q** Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

#### Naga E-Bakwit

Web application tailored to aid the City Social Welfare and Development Office of Naga City. The application aids the office in relief distribution, evacuee monitoring, evacuation monitoring, and report generation to boost the efficiency and productivity of the office during a disaster.

# Full-stack developer

- Developed the automation processes of report generation in xlsx format
- Provided proper documentation of system flow
- Developed the frontend functionalities and UI/UX
- Provided proper documentation of bugs found during alpha testing.
- Resolved bugs found and error in backend and frontend processes

#### **AWARDS**

9th place Ateneo Programming Challenge (Qualifying Round), All year levels
Ateneo De Naga University, May 2023